Wilton Historical Society Photograph Collection
Wilton History Room, Wilton Historical Society
- 3. Photograph albums and scrapbooks
  - Albums and scrapbooks in boxes
    - Ambler family, 1920s; This Elizabeth "Betty" Raymond Ambler's childhood scrapbook. It contains trade cards, newspaper clippings, and pictures of animals by Harry Whittier Frees. It is stored in a box and shelved with the bulk of the Ambler collection. (Box 75, Item 75)
    - Ambler family, 1900; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings relating to family news, President and Mrs. McKinley, Queen Victoria, the DAR, and various other topics. It likely belonged to Hannah Raymond Ambler. It is stored in a box and shelved with the bulk of the Ambler collection. (Box 76, Item 76)
    - Ambler family, 1900; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings relating to family news, local and national politics, and letterhead from hotels patronized in Washington, D.C.; Niagara Falls, New York; and Bethlehem, New Hampshire. It likely belonged to Hannah Raymond Ambler. It is stored in a box and shelved with the bulk of the Ambler collection. (Box 77, Item 77)
    - Ambler family, 1911; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings relating to family news, local and national politics, local churches, and advertisements for Elmore cars. It likely belonged to Hannah Raymond Ambler. It is stored in a box and shelved with the bulk of the Ambler collection. (Box 78, Item 78)
    - Bradley, Flora, 1905; This is a collection of postcards. It is filed out of order in a box near the Ambler collection. (Box 79, Item 49)
    - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch, 1961; This is a photograph album of a trip to England. It is filed out of order in a box. (Box 34, Item 34)
    - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch, 1950; This is a photograph album of a trip to England and Scotland. It is filed out of order in a box. (Box 32-33, Item 32)
    - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch and Fred, 1955; This is a photograph album of a trip to England, Scotland, and Wales. It is filed out of order in a box. (Box 32-33, Item 33)
    - Weitzel family, circa 1926; This is a scrapbook. It is filed out of order in a box. (Box 36, Item 36)
    - Weston family, undated; This box contains photograph albums. The original Wilton Historical Society accession numbers for these items are 2010.18.1-2010.18.3. (Box 68, Item 68)
    - Weston family, undated; This box contains photograph albums. The original Wilton Historical Society accession numbers for these items are 2010.18.4-2010.18.6. (Box 69, Item 69)
    - Weston family, undated; This box contains photograph albums and negatives. (Box 70, Item 70)
  - Albums and scrapbooks on shelves
    - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch, 1967; This is a photograph album of a Mediterranean cruise. (Box *, Item 8)
    - Fitch family, undated; This is a scrapbook of photos, newspaper clippings, correspondence, etc. (Box *, Item 1)
    - Center School, 1941; This is a scrapbook of correspondence between students and soldiers during World War Two. (Box *, Item 2)
    - Sturges family, undated; This is a scrapbook of pictures and photos with comments and clippings. (Box *, Item 3)
    - Steichen, Kate Rodina, 1968; This is a scrapbook of clippings of Hurlbutt Street School House Activities. (Box *, Item 4)
    - Wilton Volunteer Fire Department, 1978; This is a photograph album of dinners and a parade. (Box *, Item 5)
    - Burnham, Charles, 1906; This is a photograph album of the reservoir and Belden Hill area. (Box *, Item 6)
    - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch, 1964; This is a photograph album of a trip around the world. (Box *, Item 7)
    - Wilton: True Bicentennial Stories, 1975; This is photograph album. (Box *, Item 9)
    - Center School, 1942; These are scrapbooks of student efforts during World War Two, including photographs, drawings, and newspaper clippings. (Box *, Folder 11, 12)
    - Whitney, Helen, 1850; This is an autograph album. (Box *, Item 13)
    - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch, 1914; This is a photograph album of a visit to her uncle Arthur Fitch in London. (Box *, Item 14)
    - Wilton Bulletin, 1941; This is a scrapbook of World War Two articles. (Box *, Item 15)
    - Fitch family, 1731; This is a scrapbook of photos, newspaper clippings, correspondence, and notes. (Box *, Item 16)
    - Fitch, Agnes J., 1871; This is a scrapbook of drawings and newspaper clippings of Fitch family events. It includes a genealogy list. (Box *, Item 17)
    - Bedient family, undated; This is a photograph album. (Box *, Item 18)
    - Berry, Captain, 1835; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings. (Box *, Item 19)
    - Anonymous, 1860s; This is a photograph album. It is fragile. (Box *, Item 20)
    - Anonymous, 1800s; This is a photograph album. (Box *, Item 21)
    - Anonymous, 1800s; This is a photograph album. It is fragile. (Box *, Item 22)
    - DeForest family, 1985; These are photograph albums of the wedding of Myrtle Taylor Olmstead into the DeForest family. (Box *, Item 23, 24)
    - Ogden, F. Clerc, 1960; These are scrapbooks of letters and newspaper clippings relating to F. Clerc Ogden's retirement party. (Box *, Item 25, 26)
    - Olmstead, Marian (Mrs. Edward), 1880; This scrapbook contains copies of newspaper clippings and a program of the Congregational Home Missionary Society Anniversary. Original is in MAN. (Box *, Item 27)
    - Comstock-Edney family, 1906; This is a photograph album. (Box *, Item 28)
    - Belden family, 1850; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings, family photographs, correspondence, wedding announcements, death notices, etc. (Box *, Item 29)
    - Wilton Bicentennial Committee, undated; This is a scrapbook of meeting minutes. (Box *, Item 30)
    - Adams family, 1800s; This is a photograph album. (Box *, Item 31)
    - Board of Education, 1968; This is a scrapbook of meeting minutes, containing vol. 9, nos. 19-24. (Box *, Item 35)
    - Ogden, F. Clerc, 1949; This is a scrapbook of poetry, correspondence, "Old Timer" articles, and newspaper clippings of town activities. This item is MISSING. (Box *, Item 37)
    - Belden family, 1820s; This is a scrapbook of poetry, some clipped from newspapers and some handwritten. (Box *, Item 38)
    - Rundle, Abigail, 1930; This is a photograph album. (Box *, Item 39)
    - DeForest family, 1985; This is a photograph album of the wedding of Willis DeForest and Myrtle Olmstead. (Box *, Item 40)
    - DeForest, Myrtle Taylor Olmstead, 1920; This is a photograph album. (Box *, Item 41)
    - DeForest family, 1960s; This is a photograph album. (Box *, Item 42)
    - DeForest family, undated; This is a photograph album. (Box *, Item 43)
    - Fitch, Fannie, 1886; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings on Wilton happenings, deaths, weddings, etc. (Box *, Item 44)
    - Ogden, F. Clerc, 1898; This is a scrapbook titled “One Boy’s Menagerie.” It contains news articles and pictures of ships and miscellaneous incidents. This item is MISSING. (Box *, Item 45)
    - PTA Choral Club, 1935; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings, programs, and pictures. (Box *, Item 48)
    - Davenport, John, undated; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings. It was gifted by John Davenport. (Box *, Item 51)
    - Anonymous, circa 1890; This is a scrapbook of postcards and advertising cards, including many from Norwalk. (Box *, Item 52)
    - Nelson, Maud Bethel, undated; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings. (Box *, Item 53)
    - Hooker, Rev. William E. (St. Matthews), 1892; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings. It came from the Helen Gregory papers. (Box *, Item 54)
    - Wilton's Bicentennial Year, 1976; This is a scrapbook of mostly newspaper clippings, with some documents and paper ephemera. (Box *, Item 55)
    - Keeler, Mrs. W. L., 1932; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings. (Box *, Item 56)
    - St. Matthew's Episcopal Church, 1849; This is a scrapbook of church history, containing old, original documents. (Box *, Item 57)
    - Lambert Corners, 1960s; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings and original documents compiled by Doris Soldner, Wilton Historical Society curator. (Box *, Item 58)
    - Blackmar, Dana, 1943; This is a scrapbook of personal memorabilia. (Box *, Item 59)
    - Kiwanis Club of Wilton, 1994; This is a scrapbook of a Veteran's Day program (1994) and a Memorial Day program (1995). (Box *, Item 60)
    - Bald Hill Methodist Episcopal Church, North Wilton, 1822; This is a scrapbook of church records. (Box *, Item 61)
    - Villager's Club, 1960s; This is a photograph album. (Box *, Item 62)
    - Fitch family, circa 1850; This is a photograph album from the family of Arthur Treat Fitch. (Box *, Item 63)
    - Fitch family, 18751900; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings, photographs, etc., from the family of Arthur Treat Fitch. (Box *, Item 64)
    - Wilton Arts Council, 1975; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings and photographs documenting their activities. (Box *, Item 66)
    - FISH, 1968; This is a scrapbook of fliers, documents, and newspaper clippings documenting their activities. (Box *, Item 67)
    - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch, 1914; This is a notebook for a game recording the biographical details, likes and dislikes, etc., of the author's Wilton contemporaries. (Box *, Item 46)
    - Fitch, Mabel, 1895; This is Mabel Fitch's notebook from her years as a teacher. It contains transcribed poetry and newspaper clippings. (Box *, Item 47)
- 4. Miscellaneous (by topic)
  - Accidents, crimes, and disasters
    - Elm tree - Fallen in front of Congregational Church, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 8)
    - Norwalk River flooding at Lovers' Lane near old Railroad Station, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 29)
    - Lambert murder detectives, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 34)
    - Blizzard of 1888, This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 31)
    - Detectives at Lambert family house following murder, circa 1922; The address is 150 Danbury Road. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 517)
    - Blizzard of 1888 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 280)
    - Blizzard of 1888, South Norwalk, 1912 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 282)
    - Flood of 1955, Cannondale (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 395, 683)
    - Flooding - Cottage Row, circa 1918 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 87)
    - Flooding - Cottage Row, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 400)
    - Flooding - Cottage Row, 1955 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 401)
    - Flooding - Railroad Station, 1911 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 405)
    - Merwin Dam - After the storm, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 16)
    - Skunk Lane - Airplane crash, 1950s (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 206)
    - Spring flooding, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 404)
- Agriculture and livestock
  - Photographs in boxes
    - Warncke Fruit and Pickle Farm, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 3)
    - Edward O. Gilbert and dairy wagon, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 20)
    - Gunning, Thomas - grain silo, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 19)
    - Harvesting hay, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 12)
    - Three farmers in a corn field, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 10)
    - Warncke Fruit and Pickle Farm, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 22)
    - Wilton Congregational Church - Reverend Hart feeding his chickens, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 24)
    - Woman with pigs, undated; This photograph was part of a 1995 exhibit. (Box P-OS-3, Item 6)
    - Barns, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 59a, 59b)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - Abandoned farm country, 1941 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 542)
    - Ambler family farm, circa 1966 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 188)
    - Belden Hill Milk Dairy, 1910 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 495)
    - Chestnut Hill Road - Jackson family farm, 1967 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 818)
    - Cornfields, Cannondale, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 36)
    - Gunning family farm, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 251)
    - Gunning family farm, 1912 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 252)
    - Harry Jackson farm, 1967 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 168)
    - Hurlbutt family farm, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 916)
    - Jackson and Webb Fruit Growers, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 618)
    - Merwin dairy farm, circa 1950 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 813)
    - Middlebrook family fields and farm, 1906 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 30)
    - Middlebrook farm, 1948 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 86)
    - Old apple tree, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 496)
    - Painting of Weir Barn, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 660)
    - Pig slaughtering at Olmstead family farm, 1940 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 965)
    - Unidentified farm scenes, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 826)
    - View of farm field, Cannondale, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 32)
    - Warncke's Fruit and Pickle Farm, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 564, 686)
    - Wilcek Asparagus Farm, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 932)
- Business and industry
  - Photographs in boxes
    - Gilbert and Bennett Manufacturing Company employees, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 18)
    - Harre, John C. - Lambert tavern, Wilton, 1727; This is an original watercolor kept on display in the Wilton History Room. (Box P-OS-5, Item 1)
    - Harre, John C. - Marvin tavern, Pimpewaug, 1760; This is an original watercolor kept on display in the Wilton History Room. (Box P-OS-5, Item 2)
    - Harre, John C. - Wilton Motor Building / Gas Station, circa 1940; This is an original watercolor kept on display in the Wilton History Room. (Box P-OS-5, Item 9)
    - Henry Monroe blacksmith shop on Danbury Road, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 23)
    - Merwin Mill, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 17)
    - Merwin Mill Dam showing thirty feet drop to pit, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 12)
    - Meyers Mill, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 63)
    - Trough of Old Grist Mill, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 65)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - Antiques "Summer Shop" on Danbury Road, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 848)
    - Antiques store on Danbury Road, undated; File includes a postcard. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 298)
    - Antiques store on Danbury Road, circa 1960 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 559)
    - Axe factory, Weston, 1928 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 217)
    - Barrett Brothers Service Station, Georgetown, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 286)
    - Barringer Building, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 771)
    - Blacksmith Shop, circa 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 246)
    - Blacksmith shop, Cannondale, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 863)
    - Borglum Studio sign, 1994 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 98)
    - Buttery Mill, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 919)
    - Cannon General Store, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 630)
    - Carpenters and Joiners outing, 1927 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 313)
    - Crossways, circa 1935 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 705)
    - 195 Danbury Road - Wilton Inn, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 693)
    - 308 Danbury Road - Hartman Antiques, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 297)
    - 372 Danbury Road - Wragg Brothers, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 714)
    - Disbrow Motel, 1939 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 665)
    - Gates, H. D. and Company - Carriage makers, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 278)
    - Gateway Shopping Center, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 80, 81)
    - Georgetown stores, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 243)
    - Gilbert and Bennett Wire Mills employees, 1907 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 711)
    - Goetjen Moving Service, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 676)
    - Gregory, C. T. - Feed Mill and Store, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 703)
    - Gregory, C. T. and Son - Auto Store, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 594)
    - Hubbard Building, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 773)
    - Hurlbutt General Store, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 754)
    - Ice Cream Parlor, 1913 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 603)
    - Ice house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 245)
    - Keeler Building / Hardware Store, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 774)
    - Keeler General Store, Wilton Center, 1950 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 136)
    - Lockwood Factory, 1903 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 392)
    - LoFink, Jessie - Gas station, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 927)
    - Marvin Tavern, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 191)
    - Merwin Dam in winter, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 12)
    - Merwin Falls, 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 11, 15, 0438)
    - Merwin Falls and Dam, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 9)
    - Merwin's Saw Mill, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 18)
    - Meyer Mill, circa 1940 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 789)
    - Mortar and pestle, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 740)
    - National CSS, Inc. - 187 Danbury Road, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 899)
    - North Main Street in Georgetown, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 241)
    - Och's Confectionery Store, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 694)
    - Old Gregory railroad crossing, Cannondale, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 704)
    - Old Merwin Mill, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 10)
    - Old Spice / Stone Mill, Georgetown, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 97)
    - Orem's field and diner, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 572)
    - Piersall Building, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 772)
    - Piersall Building, Wilton Center, circa 1970 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 827)
    - 923 Ridgefield Road - Red Lion Inn, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 267)
    - Route 7 in Georgetown, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 99)
    - South Wilton business, 1998 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 924)
    - South Wilton Nurseries, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 312, 599)
    - Split Rock Tavern, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 699)
    - The Doll House, 1950s (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 90)
    - Tilghman and Frost, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 775)
    - Village Market, 1917; Includes a drawing and postcard. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 133)
    - Village Market, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 503)
    - Village Market, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 846)
    - Weston Toy Company, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 26)
    - Wilton Motors, Debenigno Building, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 122, 316)
- Celebrations and observances
  - Photographs in boxes
    - 4th of July Parade at Warncke Fruit and Pickle Farm, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 21)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - Civil War veterans, 1917 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 887)
    - Memorial Day Parade, 1979 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 835)
    - Thanksgiving Feast, 1922 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 606)
    - Veteran's Day, 1994 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 836)
    - Washington Bicentennial Pageant, 1932 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 651)
    - Wilton Center on Christmas Day, 1991 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 810)
- Cemeteries and churches
  - Photographs in boxes
    - Cemetery - Zion Hill Methodist Church, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 54)
    - Church - First Meeting House, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 11)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 67)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 48)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational - Shingling the chapel, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 11)
    - Harre, John C. - Zion Hill Methodist Church, 1844; This is an original watercolor kept on display in the Wilton History Room. (Box P-OS-5, Item 5)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - Cemetery - Belden family headstone, undated; File includes a negative. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 888)
    - Cemetery - Comstock, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 796)
    - Cemetery - David Dunning headstone, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 537)
    - Cemetery - DeForest, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 893)
    - Cemetery - Sharp Hill, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 185)
    - Cemetery - St. Matthews Episcopal Church, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 179)
    - Cemetery - Turner, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 557)
    - Church - Bald Hill Methodist, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 201)
    - Church - First Church of Christ, circa 1980 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 799)
    - Church - Georgetown Gilbert Memorial Chapel, undated; File includes postcards. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 166)
    - Church - Georgetown Methodist, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 171)
    - Church - Georgetown Sacred Heart, undated; File includes postcards. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 167)
    - Church - Kent Methodist, 1950 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 173)
    - Church - Our Lady of Fatima, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 933)
    - Church - St. Matthews Episcopal, undated; File includes postcards. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 180)
    - Church - St. Matthews Episcopal, 1894 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 183)
    - Church - St. Matthews Episcopal - Canterbury Market, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 905)
    - Church - St. Matthews Episcopal - Interior, 1912; File includes postcards. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 800)
    - Church - St. Matthews Episcopal - View, circa 1908 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 184)
    - Church - Weston Congregational, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 216)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational, circa 1920; File includes postcards. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 163)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational, 1964; File includes a magazine cover. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 820)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational, undated; Files include undated interior and exterior views. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 145, 150, 412)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational - Carriage barns, 1875 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 146)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational - Elm tree removal, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 155)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational - Fair, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 144)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational - First Meeting House site, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 214)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational - Interior, 1975 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 548)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational and Parish Hall, undated; Files include undated views of the parish hall. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 148, 157)
    - Church - Wilton Congregational - Christmas cards, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 170)
    - Church - Zion Hill Methodist, undated; File includes postcards. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 177)
    - Church - Zion Hill Methodist and barn, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 178)
    - 496 Danbury Road - Zion Hill Methodist Church parsonage, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 867)
    - 65 Ridgefield Road - Wilton Congregational Church parsonage and Sturges family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 164)
- Civic and social organizations
  - Photographs in boxes